<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Help -->
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_navigation_title">Navigation</string>
    <string name="help_navigation_text">
        From the home screen, swipe down to display the favorites panel and swipe up to hide it.
        \n
        \nIf you swipe up when the favorites panel is hidden, it will display the complete list of applications.
        Swipe down from the top of this list to come back to the home screen.
        \n
        \nPress the button below the favorites panel to display the menu of the launcher.
        \n
        \nIf you hold your finger a few moments on an application or a folder, you will be offered to access its settings.
    </string>
    <string name="help_notification_title">Notification</string>
    <string name="help_notification_text">
        The notification allows to display a popup with favorites above other applications when you leave the home screen.
        In most cases, it should work directly and without issues.
        \n
        \nHowever, in some special cases it may bring back to the home screen instead of being displayed over other applications.
        \nIf you are facing this issue, there are two things you can try:
        \n- Press the \"clear all\" button in Recent Apps
        \n- Reboot your smartphone
        \nAfter one of these actions, the problem should not appear again.
        \nIf it persists, I am sorry but it seems this will not work for you :-/
        \n
        \nTo not be intrusive, the notification icon is transparent and low priority.
        With some applications having even lower priorities, this may result in an empty space in the status bar.
        \n
        \nFinally, if you change the default launcher, you may still see the notification.
        To hide it, you can open Discreet Launcher (no need to be the default launcher) and disable the notification in the settings.
    </string>
    <string name="help_list_update_title">List update</string>
    <string name="help_list_update_text">
        The list of applications and their icons are refreshed only after some events
        (on start, when an application is added or removed, if the icon pack is modified).
        When this happens, a small popup message appears during a few moments.
        \n
        \nIf something does not feel right, you should try to refresh the applications list manually.
    </string>
    <string name="help_folders_title">Folders</string>
    <string name="help_folders_text">
        To create/rename/remove folders and put applications inside, you need to use the folders organizer.
        It is accessible using the menu button or by clicking on the title of an open folder.
        \n
        \nYou can create as many folders as you want to organize your applications.
        These folders can also be added in favorites.
        If a folder is removed, its content will be put back in the main applications list.
        \n
        \nAn application can be in only one folder at a time (or not in a folder).
        However, you can have both an application and the folder containing this application in favorites.
    </string>
    <string name="help_search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="help_search_text">
        The search icon allows to find an application in the complete list.
        You can add it to favorites in order to access it also using the notification.
        For technical reasons, it is not possible to add it in a folder.
        \n
        \nIf you do not plan to use it, you can also hide it like any application.
    </string>

    <!-- Changelog -->
    <string name="changelog_title">Changelog</string>
    <string name="changelog_mentions">\"@pseudo\" indicates the user who suggested the idea or reported the bug</string>
    <string name="changelog_folder">changelog-en</string>
    <string name="error_changelog_folder">The changelog folder was not found!</string>
    <string name="error_changelog_file">Error while opening %1s!</string>

</resources>
