<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Help -->
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_navigation_title">Navigation</string>
    <string name="help_navigation_text">
        Swipe down from the home screen to show favorites, and upwards to hide them.
        \n
        \nSwipe up to show all apps if the favorites panel is hidden.

        Swipe down from the top of it to return to the home screen.
        \n
        \nThe button below the favorites panel opens the launcher menu.
        \n
        \nLong-hold an app or folder to access its settings.
    </string>
    <string name="help_notification_title">Notification</string>
    <string name="help_notification_text">
        Shows a popup of favorites above other apps when you leave the home screen.
        \n
        \If instead it brings you back to the home screen:
        \n- Press the \"clear all\" button in \"Recent Apps\" or
        \n- Reboot your device
        \n
        \nUnintrusively, the notification icon is transparent and of low priority.
        With some apps having even lower priorities, this may result in empty space in the status bar.
        \n
        \nIf the Discreet Launcher notification is still there after changing to a different launcher, you can

        turn it off in the Discreet Launcher settings.
    </string>
    <string name="help_list_update_title">List update</string>
    <string name="help_list_update_text">
        Refreshing the app list and icons shows a small popup message, it also happens
        when starting, when an app is added or removed, or if the icon pack is modified.
    </string>
    <string name="help_folders_title">Folders</string>
    <string name="help_folders_text">
        Use the folder organizer from the menu button or click the title of an open folder
        to create, rename, favorite it or any app, and/or put an app in it.
        \nRemoving folders returns all their apps to the main app list.


    </string>
    <string name="help_search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="help_search_text">
        The search icon lets you find any app, and can be favorited to be available

        from the notification, or hidden.
        \n
        \nIf there is only one search result, pressing \"Enter\" opens it.
    </string>

    <!-- Changelog -->
    <string name="changelog_title">Changelog</string>
    <string name="changelog_mentions">\"@pseudo\" indicates the user who suggested the idea or reported the bug</string>
    <string name="changelog_folder">changelog-en</string>
    <string name="error_changelog_folder">Could not find the changelog folder</string>
    <string name="error_changelog_file">Could not open %1s</string>

</resources>
